export default [
    {
        question: 'Which declaration defines this document to be HTML5?',
        options: ['<!DOCTYPE html>', '<html>', '<head>', '<title>', '<body>'],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Which element is the root element of an HTML page?',
        options: ['<p>', '<h1>', '<body>', '<title>', '<html>'],
        correct: 4
    },    
    {
        question: 'Which element contains meta information about the document?',
        options: ['<title>', '<head>', '<body>', '<h1>', '<p>'],
        correct: 1
    },    
    {
        question: 'Which element specifies a title for the document?',
        options: ['<!DOCTYPE html>', '<p>', '<title>', '<body>', '<h1>'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which element contains the visible page content?',
        options: ['<p>', '<h1>', '<title>', '<head>', '<body>'],
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which element defines a large heading?',
        options: ['<html>', '<head>', '<h1>', '<title>', '<body>'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which element defines a paragraph?',
        options: ['<html>', '<head>', '<title>', '<p>', '<body>'],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Which element defines a hyperlink?',
        options: ['<body>', '<html>', '<p>', '<head>', '<a>'],
        correct: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which element defines an image?',
        options: ['<head>', '<title>', '<img>', '<a>', '<html>'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which element defines a table?',
        options: ['<p>', '<html>', '<head>', '<title>', '<table>'],
        correct: 4
    }
]